Many have thought Israel wants to ban TikTok, and the truth is Israel is trying to buy TikTok.
I want to be very clear, the government of Israel is not buying TikTok,
but individuals very closely aligned with Israel, former Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin.
I think it should be sold. I understand the technology. It's a great business,
and I'm going to put together a group to buy TikTok.
You're trying to buy TikTok?
I am, because this should be owned by U.S. businesses.
There's no way that the Chinese would ever let a U.S. company own something like this in China.
You say, have you already put a group together?
No, I'm working. You're excited.
Explore your group.
I've spoken to a bunch of people.
Steven Mnuchin is an ardent Zionist. Back in January, he made a statement saying
they're looking for significant investment opportunities in Israel.
He's very closely affiliated with AIPAC and led pro-Israel lobbying movements himself.
Of course, the biggest concern was the anti-Israel bias on TikTok,
which is exactly why they plan to change the algorithm.
The technology, I won't go into all the details, but the app needs to be rebuilt in the U.S.
It needs to be U.S. technology.
I think there's a lot that could be done in six months,
but I would work closely with the U.S. and with China.
A few days after headlines go crazy stating there's a counter to AIPAC,
individuals that are part of the Israeli lobby in the United States are stating they want to buy TikTok.
Many of us have heard the leaked audio from Jonathan Greenblatt,
the CEO of the Anti-Defamation League.
Seems the Israel lobby is doing exactly what they stated,
a lot faster than any of us would have assumed.
You're right.
A lot faster than any of us would have responded here last night at a time.
I have a few days after a while.
But I'm around the country,
and I need to screw up your mind.
I need to screw in this video.
I have no idea you're going to call this guy.
And I love youku who does that make azel message.
And I know I know I know thePR,
but maybe hold the money back to every time I already said that,
you know I know I'm getting a little one.
Let's go live a little by a soul now.